

Summary.

Experienced technical leader and engineer, with broad experience in building products from inception to shipping, using a wide variety of technologies. Proven ability to grow and develop teams, improve processes and lead to successful product delivery.

Education

University of Washington

Seattle, WA

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Sept. 2010 - June 2012

Brown University

Providence, RI

B.Sc. in Computer Science, B.A. in Economics

Sept. 2004 - May 2008

Oxford University

Oxford, UK

VISITING STUDENT AT ST. EDMUND'S HALL / OXFORD COMPUTING LABORATORY

Jan. 2007 - June 2007

Experience _____

Splunk

Seattle, WA

DIRECTOR OF ENGINEERING 2013 - PRESENT

- Engineering leadership for the Seattle office, drove growth from four people to over sixty today, including interviewing a majority of the office.
- Managed, hired and developed a team of engineers ranging in seniority from junior to principal engineers.
- Driving technical and product strategy for Splunk for the Developer Platform.
- Led and architected several critical technical initiatives, including HTTP ingestion, Splunk's KV Store API, and improvements to Splunk's manageability and scaleability.
- Global engineering release lead for multiple Splunk releases.
- Initiated and drove multiple cross-organizational initiatives to improve Splunk's engineering process, such source control, code reviews, continuous integration and interviewing.
- · Part of several technology and architecture evaluations, both internal and external, for forward-looking initiatives.

Splunk Seattle, WA

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2011 - 2013

- Founding engineer of Splunk's Seattle, the first office out of the Bay Area.
- Led technical direction and architecture for our Developer Platform initiative, including Splunk's SDKs, Tooling and Web Framework.
- Lead developer for several of our SDKs and the Splunk Web Framework.

Microsoft Redmond, WA

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER II - TECHNICAL STRATEGY INCUBATION (MIDORI)

2008 - 2011

- Designed and implemented a capability-based security system for low-level resources in a next- generation operating system.
- Designing and implementing synergistic scenarios between OS and hypervisor, including enlightened video and debugging services.
- Involved in design and implementation of various aspects of system, from low-level subsystems to high-level applications and services.

Microsoft Redmond, WA

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER INTERN - MEDIA FOUNDATION/WINDOWS EXPERIENCE

Jun. 2007 - Aug. 2007

- · Developed multimedia playback scenario in Media Foundation and Windows Media Player, shipped as part of Windows 7.
- Implemented metadata solution through Media Foundation for new media format.

Speaking.

Apr 2012 JSConf US Scottsdale, AZ

Splunk + JavaScript: bringing your data to life

Nov 2012 CascadiaJS Seattle, WA

Realtime Big Data makes real data big time: https://youtu.be/r0TVWW8316E

ongoing **Splunk** US.

Multiple Splunk speaking engagements, audiences ranging from 10 to a 1000

Other.

Languages English (Fluent), Hebrew (Fluent)

Awards Splunk BUILD MVP, Splunk Values Award - Innovation